[
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95033b",
    "correctAnswer": "Althea Gibson",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Venus Williams",
      "Serena Williams",
      "Maureen Dalyweather"
    ],
    "question": "Who was the first African-American female to win a Wimbledon Tennis event?",
    "tags": [
      "firsts",
      "tennis",
      "people",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501df",
    "correctAnswer": "Francis Ford Coppola",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg",
      "Woody Allen",
      "Martin Scorsese"
    ],
    "question": "Which director directed The Godfather?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f95163f",
    "correctAnswer": "Hand",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Foot",
      "Swarm",
      "Flock"
    ],
    "question": "What is the name for a cluster or bunch of bananas?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "words",
      "general_knowledge",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "636a52ae990390307063f3b4",
    "correctAnswer": "The Top Notes",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bob Marley and The Wailers",
      "William Shatner",
      "Gary Jules and Michael Andrews"
    ],
    "question": "The song 'Twist and Shout' had a well-known cover by The Beatles, but who recorded the original?",
    "tags": [
      "music",
      "cover_song",
      "songs",
      "musicians"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501cd",
    "correctAnswer": "Anne of Green Gables",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Glass Bead Game",
      "Heidi",
      "The Boy in the Striped Pyjamas"
    ],
    "question": "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'Mrs. Rachel Lynde lived just where the Avonlea main road dipped down into a little hollow, fringed with alders and ladies' eardrops and traversed by a brook that had its source away back in the woods of the old Cuthbert place;'?",
    "tags": [
      "literature",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9517c2",
    "correctAnswer": "Apple Bobbing",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trick or Treating",
      "Jack o' Lanterns",
      "Wearing Scary Outfits"
    ],
    "question": "Which Halloween tradition originated from a custom to establish who would get married first?",
    "tags": [
      "halloween",
      "traditions",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502b7",
    "correctAnswer": "HoneyÂ ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Almond",
      "Grape",
      "Potato"
    ],
    "question": "What Is the Main Ingredient Of The Liquor Mead? ",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b07",
    "correctAnswer": "Take That",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Talk Talk",
      "Feeder",
      "Bring Me the Horizon"
    ],
    "question": "Which band includes 'Robbie Williams'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9511c3",
    "correctAnswer": "Stigmata",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Holy Molies",
      "Psalms",
      "Anaschsim"
    ],
    "question": "Which word refers to the appearance of wounds in places that correspond to the crucifixion wounds of Christ?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "society_and_culture",
      "christianity",
      "religion"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950338",
    "correctAnswer": "Constantine",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Justinian",
      "Claudius",
      "Julius"
    ],
    "question": "Who Was The First Christian Emperor Of Rome?",
    "tags": [
      "christianity",
      "romans",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "6233860d62eaad73716a8cad",
    "correctAnswer": "Venezuela",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Canada",
      "Zimbabwe",
      "Australia"
    ],
    "question": "Where is Angel Falls?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "639ae36d929b90846f2fc8d0",
    "correctAnswer": "Maize",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rice",
      "Wheat",
      "Barley"
    ],
    "question": "What type of food was the most important staple of the Aztec diet?",
    "tags": [
      "history",
      "aztecs",
      "food"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "62611fd14b176d54800e3d73",
    "correctAnswer": "1955",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1947",
      "1963",
      "1971"
    ],
    "question": "In which year did Rosa Parks refuse to give up her seat in protest of racial inequality?",
    "tags": [
      "events",
      "civil_rights",
      "usa",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c604a50d1a5e051325a50",
    "correctAnswer": "Kabuli Pulao",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frikadeller",
      "Ema Datshi",
      "Masala Dosa"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these dishes would you most expect to find in Afghanistan?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fcb3",
    "correctAnswer": "Indo-European",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Koreanic",
      "Sino-Tibetan",
      "Austronesian"
    ],
    "question": "The language 'Sinhalese' belongs to which language family?",
    "tags": [
      "language",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504ea",
    "correctAnswer": "nematodes",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Japanese people",
      "earthquakes",
      "the relationship of organisms to each other and to their environment"
    ],
    "question": "What is Nematology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95006a",
    "correctAnswer": "Evander Holyfield",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mike Tyson",
      "Oscar De La Hoya",
      "Floyd Mayweather"
    ],
    "question": "Which Heavweight Boxer Was Known As The Real Deal?",
    "tags": [
      "boxing",
      "people",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6293ec6f7f41d6338b96eef0",
    "correctAnswer": "Joseph Lister",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Faraday",
      "Benny Russell",
      "Franz Jacob"
    ],
    "question": "Which surgeon pioneered the use of sterilisation and antiseptic surgery?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "history",
      "society_and_culture",
      "medicine"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6262886b4b176d54800e3d9b",
    "correctAnswer": "Budweiser",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guinness",
      "Stella Artois",
      "Corona"
    ],
    "question": "Which beer brand is associated with the marketing slogan 'King of Beers'?",
    "tags": [
      "business",
      "marketing",
      "drink",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b89",
    "correctAnswer": "The Jimi Hendrix Experience",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poison",
      "The Pussycat Dolls",
      "Three 6 Mafia"
    ],
    "question": "Which English-American psychedelic rock band released the song 'Purple Haze'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951b3c",
    "correctAnswer": "1945",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1938",
      "1940",
      "1943"
    ],
    "question": "In what year of WW II did Russia declare war on Japan?",
    "tags": [
      "world_war_2",
      "russia",
      "japan",
      "wars",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950868",
    "correctAnswer": "Guinea",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guinea-Bissau",
      "Ivory Coast",
      "The Gambia"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Sierra Leone?",
    "tags": [
      "geography"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502b0",
    "correctAnswer": "RiceÂ ",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spinach",
      "Paneer",
      "Basa"
    ],
    "question": "What Is The Principle Ingredient Of Biryani?",
    "tags": [
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f76",
    "correctAnswer": "Stephen King",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "H. P. Lovecraft",
      "Edgar Allan Poe",
      "Jack Vance"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Nightmares & Dreamscapes'?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504e5",
    "correctAnswer": "numbers",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "wounds and injuries caused by accidents or assaults and their surgical treatment and repair",
      "psychotropic or psychiatric drugs",
      "Egyptian hieroglyphics, an ancient writing system"
    ],
    "question": "What is Numerology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c8b",
    "correctAnswer": "Metallica",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice Cooper",
      "The Pussycat Dolls",
      "Three 6 Mafia"
    ],
    "question": "Which American heavy metal band released the studio album 'Master of Puppets'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ffd1",
    "correctAnswer": "The Rolling Stones",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Black",
      "Sticky Fingers",
      "Brown Sugar"
    ],
    "question": "What was the title of the first album released by The Rolling Stones?",
    "tags": [
      "music_albums",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95035d",
    "correctAnswer": "William The Conqueror",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Henry VIII",
      "Victoria",
      "Albert the Great"
    ],
    "question": "Who was crowned King of England at Westminster Abbey on Christmas day 1066?",
    "tags": [
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6357fd1168bd5000211e7179",
    "correctAnswer": "Portuguese",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hindi",
      "Berber",
      "Gujarati"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these languages would you find spoken in Angola?",
    "tags": [
      "language",
      "linguistics",
      "society_and_culture"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95018a",
    "correctAnswer": "Tarzan",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spiderman",
      "Scooby Doo",
      "Buggs Bunny"
    ],
    "question": "What famous character did Edgar Rice Burroughs create?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "62443734746187c5e7be933b",
    "correctAnswer": "It is used as an ingredient in baking.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "It is used in liquid fertilizers, potassium soaps and detergents.",
      "It is used in laundry detergent.",
      "It is used to relieve pain."
    ],
    "question": "What is the chemical sodium bicarbonate often used for?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbf9",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Oh, no, it wasn't the airplanes. It was Beauty killed the Beast.\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"Louis, I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship.\"",
      "\"Thatâs my secret, Captain: Iâm always angry.\"",
      "\"Oh, Jerry, don't let's ask for the moon. We have the stars.\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'King Kong'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507a2",
    "correctAnswer": "Julia Roberts",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Meryl Streep",
      "Sandra Bullock",
      "Anne Hathaway"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featured in films including Erin Brockovich and Ocean's Eleven?",
    "tags": [
      "acting",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625740499da29df7b05f73d2",
    "correctAnswer": "An old man travels in his house equipped with balloons, inadvertently taking a young stowaway.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A sole survivor tells of the twisty events leading up to a horrific gun battle on a boat.",
      "In the future, a small waste-collecting robot inadvertently embarks on a space journey.",
      "A man deeply immersed in the Edinburgh drug scene tries to clean up and get out."
    ],
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie Up?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b88",
    "correctAnswer": "Eagles",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Pussycat Dolls",
      "Three 6 Mafia",
      "The Velvet Underground"
    ],
    "question": "Which band includes 'Don Henley'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f5b",
    "correctAnswer": "Isaac Asimov",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ursula K. Le Guin",
      "Philip K. Dick",
      "Stephen King"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Foundation and Empire'?",
    "tags": [
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8a0",
    "correctAnswer": "Boxing",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cricket",
      "Rugby Union",
      "Ice Hockey"
    ],
    "question": "With which sport is Manny Pacquiao associated?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "general_knowledge",
      "sport"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f950fd6",
    "correctAnswer": "Jellyfish",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Squid",
      "Shark",
      "Whale"
    ],
    "question": "Which type of animal are the Sea Wasp and Cubozoa?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f95185f",
    "correctAnswer": "Robben Island",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bishop Island",
      "Truncheon Island",
      "Carril Island"
    ],
    "question": "Where was Nelson Mandela held in prison?",
    "tags": [
      "africa",
      "people",
      "islands",
      "history"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951026",
    "correctAnswer": "Entomology",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Botany",
      "Zoology",
      "Horticulture"
    ],
    "question": "What Is The Study Of Insects Called? ",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "animals",
      "biology",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c7e",
    "correctAnswer": "U2",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Public Image Ltd.",
      "The Script",
      "The Cure"
    ],
    "question": "Which Irish rock band released the studio album 'All That You Can't Leave Behind'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950148",
    "correctAnswer": "Ernest Hemmingway",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Joseph Conrad",
      "Anthony Burgess",
      "George Orwell"
    ],
    "question": "Whose first collection of short stories entitled \"In Our Time\" was published in 1925?",
    "tags": [
      "literature",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "624c6176badf21197f98f77e",
    "correctAnswer": "Pepperpot",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Plov",
      "Cou Cou and Flying Fish",
      "Shawarma"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these dishes would you most expect to find in Guyana?",
    "tags": [
      "food",
      "south_america",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f95163e",
    "correctAnswer": "Green",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blue",
      "Yellow",
      "Red"
    ],
    "question": " What colour is creme de menthe?",
    "tags": [
      "drink",
      "food_and_drink"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c9e",
    "correctAnswer": "The Rolling Stones",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "McFly",
      "Delirious?",
      "Depeche Mode"
    ],
    "question": "Which English rock band released the album 'Exile on Main St.'?",
    "tags": [
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f975",
    "correctAnswer": "The Stranger",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "One Hundred Years of Solitude",
      "The Trial",
      "The Quiet American"
    ],
    "question": "Which book contains the character 'Meursault'?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "fictitious_characters",
      "arts_and_literature"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950566",
    "correctAnswer": "demons",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the study and design of machines at the molecular level",
      "the causes and treatment of allergies; a branch of medicine",
      "organic particles, such as bacteria, fungal spores, very small insects and pollen"
    ],
    "question": "What is Demonology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd81",
    "correctAnswer": "Irving Berlin",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stephen Sondheim",
      "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
      "George Gershwin"
    ],
    "question": "Who Wrote The Musical \"There's No Business Like Show Business\"?",
    "tags": [
      "musicals",
      "theater",
      "music"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa98",
    "correctAnswer": "PenÃ©lope Cruz",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Amy Adams",
      "Viola Davis",
      "Taraji P. Henson"
    ],
    "question": "Who won the 2008 Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress for playing the role of Maria Elena in Vicky Cristina Barcelona?",
    "tags": [
      "academy_awards",
      "film",
      "acting",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950597",
    "correctAnswer": "crayfish",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "is concerned with earth materials that can be utilized for economic and/or industrial purposes",
      "same as Aetiology",
      "the laws and phenomena of aqueous vapors"
    ],
    "question": "What is Astacology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  }
]